{
    "subject": "resource/Federal_Institute_for_Risk_Assessment",
    "predicate": "property/headquarters",
    "object": "resource/Berlin",
    "human_readable": "The headquarters of Federal Institute for Risk Assessment is in Berlin.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9887133836746216,
            "question": "Is the Federal Institute for Risk Assessment headquartered in Berlin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9359184503555298,
            "question": "Where is the headquarters of the Federal Institute for Risk Assessment located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.908072829246521,
            "question": "What is the location of the Federal Institute for Risk Assessment's headquarters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8776289224624634,
            "question": "What city houses the headquarters of the Federal Institute for Risk Assessment?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7706025242805481,
            "question": "What city serves as the base for the Federal Institute for Risk Assessment?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7684399485588074,
            "question": "In which German city is the Federal Institute for Risk Assessment based?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7667776942253113,
            "question": "Which organization's headquarters are found in Berlin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7430377006530762,
            "question": "Where is the main office of the Federal Institute for Risk Assessment situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6169986128807068,
            "question": "Where can you find the Federal Institute for Risk Assessment's main offices?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3759528398513794,
            "question": "What institution has its main office in Berlin?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The headquarters of Federal Institute for Risk Assessment is in Berlin.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2897_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can you find the Federal Institute for Risk Assessment's main offices?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2897_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is the main office of the Federal Institute for Risk Assessment situated?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2897_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which organization's headquarters are found in Berlin?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2897_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2897_128.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2897_141.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2897_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2897_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2897_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2897_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2897_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2897_93.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2897_96.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2897_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe document at file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2897/re-ranker-msmarco/98.txt states that \"All locations [of BfR] can be easily reached by public transport (bus, S-Bahn, U-Bahn (underground), regional train).  We recommend our visitors to use this upon arrival.\" and later mentions that the headquarter is in Berlin-Jungfernheide. This implies that while not directly stating it, the headquarters of Federal Institute for Risk Assessment (BfR) are indeed located in Berlin, specifically in the Jungfernheide site."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that the German Federal Institute for Risk Assessment (BfR) has multiple locations in Berlin, including a headquarter in Berlin-Jungfernheide. This supports the statement that the headquarters of the Federal Institute for Risk Assessment is in Berlin."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}